iphonedownloadblog.com 2017-06-24

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the iDownloadBlog.com website, its mobile application, our email newsletter, and other applications owned and operated by iDownloadBlog.com (collectively referred to as the “iDB Services”), and to any services that display this notice. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to “iDB,” “iDownloadBlog,” and “iDownloadBlog.com” include iDownloadBlog.com and its mobile application.

## Email addresses

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share your email with any third party.

## Ownership of information

iDownloadBlog is the sole owner of any information collected on our website.

## Comments/message boards

iDB Services contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party and not used for any other purpose. In short, we will not send you unwanted emails.

## Push notifications

Readers can opt in to receive push notifications every time a new article is published. We do not collect any information from you and anyone can unsubscribe at any time by following [these steps](http://www.idownloadblog.com/push/) for the Safari Push notifications, or [these steps](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201925) for the iDB app notifications.

## Email newsletter

Readers can opt in to [receive email newsletters](http://feedburner.google.com/fb/a/mailverify?uri=iphonedlb&loc=en_US). The email addresses collected for this are handled by Feedburner, a service by Google. We do not use your email address for anything else but sending you this newsletter. If you wish to unsubscribe, please see the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the newsletter you receive.

## Cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies

iDB Services may use cookies, or similar technologies to manage users’ site preferences and ensure the site and application’s functionality. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our website or mobile application is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

## Third-party cookies

iDB and its advertisers may also use ad network providers and other service providers to help present customized content and advertisements on the website. These providers may use cookies, or similar technologies on your computer to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their content and advertisements, using data gathered over time and across their networks of web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audience.

iDB may share certain non-personally identifiable information about you as an iDownloadBlog.com user (such as user age and zip code) with certain ad network and service providers to help them deliver more relevant content and advertisements through their networks. The use of cookies, or similar technologies by ad networks and content providers is subject to their own privacy policies, not that of iDownloadBlog.

## Traffic reports

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

## Legal proceedings

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but iDownloadBlog may need to disclose information when required by law.

## Links

iDownloadBlog frequently links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our website we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy.

## Children’s privacy

iDB services are intended for a general audience and are not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and we do not target iDB services to children under the age of 13.

## Contact information

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.idownloadblog.com/contact/).

_Last Updated: 05/05/2017_
